English German French Spanish Italian Dutch Turkish Polish Greek Portugese Croatian Albanian Serbian Bulgarian Romanian Hungarian Norwegian Persian Japanese Vietnamese Czech 

====================================================================================================================================

Terms of Use
------------

This ClipConverter Service Agreement describes the terms and conditions on which www.clipconverter.cc ("ClipConverter") offer services to you. ClipConverter is operated by Lunaweb GmbH, Gruenwald / Germany. By using ClipConverter services, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions:

1. The use of ClipConverter is governed by German law with the following modifications and explanations to be considered.
2. You are the only responsible for the data (e.g. URLs) which it sends to the ClipConverter service. One is reminded that the illicit exchanges of recordings and protected works as well as the hacking harm artistic creation. One is reminded that also non the respect of the laws in force, in particular those concerning the respect of the intellectual and artistic property, can give place to continuations and judgments.
3. ClipConverter is meant for creating a recording / copy of downloadable online videos for the personal use ("fair use"). Any further use of the content downloaded / recorded by ClipConverter, particularly but not exclusively making the content publicly accessible or using it commercially, must be agreed upon with the holder of the rights of the respective downloaded content. The user bears full responsibility for all actions related to the data transmitted by ClipConverter. ClipConverter does not grant any rights to the contents, as it only acts as a technical service provider.
4. The user carries the responsibility for checking the legitimacy of his use of ClipConverter. The legitimacy of using this service may differ in the users country through local laws. ClipConverter only provides the technical platform. Hence, ClipConverter does not take liability towards the user or any third party for the permissibility of downloading content through ClipConverter.
5. ClipConverter is a free service, which does not offer any guarantee of any kind as for its use.
6. ClipConverter reserves the right to change or discontinue any of the Services at any time.
7. The legal venue shall, if admissible, be Munich, Germany.

Privacy
-------

As of March 2023

1. Identity and contact details of the data controller
2. Contact details of the data protection officer
3. General information on data processing
4. Rights of the data subject
5. Provision of website and creation of log files
6. Use of cookies
7. Contact via Email
8. Corporate web profiles on social networks
9. Hosting
10. Geotargeting
11. Affiliate programs
12. Content delivery networks

##### I. Identity and contact details of the data controller

The data controller responsible in accordance with the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of the European Union and other data protection regulations is:

Lunaweb GmbH

Nördliche Münchner Straße 14a

82031 Grünwald

Germany

+49 89 30669804

info@clipconverter.cc

https://www.clipconverter.cc

##### II. Contact details of the data protection officer

The designated data protection officer is:

DataCo GmbH

Dachauer Str. 65

80335 Munich

Germany

+49 89 7400 45840

##### III. General information on data processing

1\. Scope of processing personal data

In general, we only process the personal data of our users to the extent necessary to provide a functioning website with our content and services. The regular processing of personal data only takes place with the consent of the user. Exceptions include cases where prior consent cannot be technically obtained and where the processing of the data is permitted by law.

2\. Legal basis for data processing

Where consent is appropriate for processing personal data, Art. 6 (1) (1) (a) GDPR serves as the legal basis to obtain the consent of the data subject for the processing of their data.

As for the processing of personal data required for the performance of a contract of which the data subject is party, Art. 6 (1) (1) (b) GDPR serves as the legal basis. This also applies to processing operations required to carry out pre-contractual activities.

When it is necessary to process personal data in order to fulfil a legal obligation to which our company is subject, Art. 6 (1) (1) (c) GDPR serves as the legal basis.

If vital interests of the data subject or another natural person require the processing of personal data, Art. 6 (1) (1) (d) GDPR serves as the legal basis.

If the processing of data is necessary to safeguard the legitimate interests of our company or that of a third party, and the fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject do not outweigh the interest of the former, Art. 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR will serve as the legal basis for the processing of data.

3\. Data removal and storage duration

The personal data of the data subject will be erased or restricted as soon as the purpose of its storage has been accomplished. Additional storage may occur if this is provided for by the European or national legislator within the EU regulations, law, or other relevant regulations to which the data controller is subject. Restriction or erasure of the data also takes place when the storage period stipulated by the aforementioned standards expires, unless there is a need to prolong the storage of the data for the purpose of concluding or fulfiling the respective contract.

##### IV. Rights of the data subject

When your personal data is processed, you are a data subject within the meaning of the GDPR and have the following rights:

1\. Right of access (Art. 15 GDPR)

You may request the data controller to confirm whether your personal data is processed by them.

If such processing occurs, you can request the following information from the data controller:

* Purposes of processing
* Categories of personal data being processed.
* Recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed.
* Planned storage period or the criteria for determining this period
* The existence of the rights of rectification, erasure or restriction or opposition.
* The existence of the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
* If applicable, origin of the data (if collected from a third party).
* If applicable, existence of automated decision-making including profiling with meaningful information about the logic involved, the scope and the effects to be expected.
* If applicable, transfer of personal data to a third country or international organization.

2\. Right to rectification (Art. 16 GDPR)

You have a right to rectification and/or modification of the data, if your processed personal data is incorrect or incomplete. The data controller must correct the data without delay

3\. Right to the restriction of processing (Art. 18 GDPR)

You may request the restriction of the processing of your personal data under the following conditions:

* If you challenge the accuracy of your personal data for a period that enables the data controller to verify the accuracy of your personal data.
* The processing is unlawful, and you oppose the erasure of the personal data and instead request the restriction of their use instead.
* The data controller or its representative no longer need the personal data for the purpose of processing, but you need it to assert, exercise or defend legal claims; or
* If you have objected to the processing pursuant and it is not yet certain whether the legitimate interests of the data controller override your interests.

4\. Right to erasure ("Right to be forgotten") (Art. 17 GDPR)

If you request from the data controller to delete your personal data without undue delay, they are required to do so immediately if one of the following applies:

* Personal data concerning you is no longer necessary for the purposes for which they were collected or processed.
* You withdraw your consent on which the processing is based pursuant to and where there is no other legal basis for processing the data.
* You object to the processing of the data and there are no longer overriding legitimate grounds for processing, or you object pursuant to Art. 21 (2) GDPR.
* Your personal data has been processed unlawfully.
* The personal data must be deleted to comply with a legal obligation in Union law or Member State law to which the data controller is subject.
* Your personal data was collected in relation to information society services offered pursuant to Art. 8 (1) GDPR.

The right to deletion does not exist if the processing is necessary

* to exercise the right to freedom of speech and information;
* to fulfil a legal obligation required by the law of the Union or Member States to which the data controller is subject, or to perform a task of public interest or in the exercise of public authority delegated to the representative.
* for reasons of public interest in the field of public health.
* for archival purposes of public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or for statistical purposes.
* to enforce, exercise or defend legal claims.

5\. Right to data portability

You have the right to receive your personal data given to the data controller in a structured and machine-readable format. In addition, you have the right to transfer this data to another person without hindrance by the data controller who was initially given the data, if:

6\. Right to object

For reasons that arise from your particular situation, you have, at any time, the right to object to the processing of your personal data pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (1) (e) or 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR; this also applies to profiling based on these provisions.

If the personal data relating to you are processed for direct marketing purposes, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of your personal data in regard to such advertising; this also applies to profiling associated with direct marketing.

7\. Right to complain to a supervisory authority

Without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you consider that the processing of personal data concerning you infringes the GDPR. The supervisory authority to which the complaint has been lodged shall inform the complainant of the status and outcome of the complaint, including the possibility of a judicial remedy under Art. 78 GDPR. A list, of the locally competent supervisory authorities in Germany can be found on the website of the Federal Commissioner for Data Protection at the following link: [https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Service/Anschriften/Laender/Laender-node.html](https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Service/Anschriften/Laender/Laender-node.html)

##### V. Provision of website and creation of log files

1\. Description and scope of data processing

Each time our website is accessed, our system automatically collects data and relevant information from the computer system of the calling device.

The following data is collected:

* Browser type and version used
* The user's operating system
* The IP address of the user
* Date and time of access
* Web pages from which the user’s system accessed our website

This data is stored in the log files of our system. This data is not stored together with other personal data of the user.

2\. Purpose of data processing

The temporary storage of the IP address by the system is necessary for the delivery of the website to the computer of the user. For this purpose, the user’s IP address must be kept for the duration of the session.

The storage in logfiles is done to ensure the functionality of the website. The data is also used to optimize the website and to ensure the security of our IT systems. An analysis of the data for marketing purposes does not take place.

For the aforementioned purposes, our legitimate interest lies in the processing of data in compliance with Art. 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR.

3\. Legal basis for data processing

The legal basis for the temporary storage of data and logfiles is Art. 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR.

4\. Duration of storage

The data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary for the purpose of its collection. The session is complete when the collection of data for the provision of the website is accomplished.

If the data is stored in log files, this is the case after seven days at the latest. Storage beyond this is possible. In this case, the IP addresses of the users are deleted or alienated so that an assignment of the calling client is not possible.

5\. Objection and removal

The collection of data for the provision of the website and the storage of the data in log files is absolutely necessary for the operation of the website. The user can object to this. Whether the objection is successful is to be determined within the framework of a balancing of interests.

##### VI. Use of cookies

1\. Description and scope of data processing

When you visit our website, we use technical tools for various functions, in particular cookies, which can be stored on your device. When you visit our website for the first time and at any time later, you have the choice of whether you generally permit the setting of cookies or which individual additional functions you would like to select. You can make changes in your browser settings or via our consent manager. Cookies are text files or information in a database that are stored on your hard drive and assigned to the browser you are using so that certain information can be passed to the entity that sets the cookie. Below we describe what kind of cookies we use:

We use technically necessary cookies, which are required for the technical structure of the website. Without these cookies, our website cannot be displayed (completely correctly) or the support functions are not possible.

The following data is stored and transmitted in the technical necessary cookies:

* Language settings
* Functionality of the website

2\. Purpose of data processing

The purpose of using technically necessary cookies is to ensure the functionality of our website. Some functions of our website cannot be offered without the use of cookies. For these, it is necessary that the browser is recognized even after a page change.

We need technical necessary cookies for the following purposes:

* Applying language settings
* Functionality of the website

3\. Legal basis for data processing

The regulations of the Telecommunications-Telemedia Data Protection Act (TTDSG) are relevant for the storage of information in the end user's terminal equipment and/or access to information already stored in the end user's terminal equipment. If the setting and reading of cookies is technically necessary, this is done to ensure the functionality of our website. In this case, the storage of and access to cookies on your terminal equipment is carried out on the basis of § 25(2)(2) TTDSG. This storage of and access to the information in your terminal equipment serves to facilitate your use of our website and to be able to offer you our services as you have requested. Some functions of our website also do not work without the use of these cookies and could therefore not be offered. The cookies are generally deleted after the session ends (e.g. logging out or closing the browser) or after the expiry of a specified duration. Information on different storage periods for cookies can be found in the following sections of this data protection declaration.

##### VII. Contact via Email

1\. Description and scope of data processing

You can contact us via the email address provided on our website. In this case the personal data of the user transmitted with the email will be stored.

The data will be used exclusively for the processing of the conversation.

2\. Purpose of data processing

If you contact us via email, this also constitutes the necessary legitimate interest in the processing of the data.

3\. Legal basis for data processing

The legal basis for the processing of data transmitted in the course of sending an e-mail is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR. Our legitimate interest is to optimally answer your request that you send by e-mail.

If the purpose of the email contact is to conclude a contract, the additional legal basis for the processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR.

4\. Duration of storage

The data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was collected. For personal data sent by email, this is the case when the respective conversation with the user has ended. The conversation ends when it can be concluded from the circumstances that the matter in question has been conclusively resolved.

The additional personal data collected during the sending process will be deleted after a period of seven days at the latest.

5\. Objection and removal

The user has the possibility to withdraw consent to the processing of their personal data at any time. If the user contacts us by email, he can object to the storage of his personal data at any time.

In this case, all personal data stored while establishing contact will be deleted.

To revoke consent contact us via support@clipconverter.cc

##### VIII. Corporate web profiles on social networks

Use of corporate profiles on social networks

**Twitter:**

Twitter International Company, One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2, Ireland

On our company profile we provide information and offer Instagram users the possibility of communication. If you carry out an action on our Instagram company profile (e.g. comments, contributions, likes etc.), you may make personal data (e.g. clear name or photo of your user profile) public. However, as we generally or to a large extent have no influence on the processing of your personal data by Instagram, we cannot make any binding statements regarding the purpose and scope of the processing of your data.

Our corporate profile in social networks is used for communication and information exchange with (potential) customers. We use the company's profile for:

Product updates

Publications on the company profile can contain the following content:

* Information about products
* Information about services
* Customer contact

Every user is free to publish personal data.

As far as we process your personal data in order to evaluate your online behavior, to offer you sweepstakes or to conduct lead campaigns, this is done on the basis of your express declaration of consent, Art. 6 (1) (1) (a), Art. 7 GDPR. The legal basis for processing personal data for the purpose of communicating with customers and interested parties is Art. 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR. Thereby, our legitimate interest is to answer your request optimally or to be able to provide the requested information. If the aim of contacting you is to conclude a contract, the additional legal basis for the processing is Art. 6 (1) (1) (b) GDPR.

The data generated on the company profile are not stored in our own systems.

For the processing of your personal data in third countries, we have provided appropriate guarantees in form of standard data protection clauses pursuant to Art. 46(2)(c) GDPR. A copy of the standard data protection clauses can be requested from us.

You can object at any time to the processing of your personal data that we collect within the framework of your use of our Twitter corporate web profile and assert your rights as a data subject mentioned under IV. of this privacy policy. Please send us an informal email to support@clipconverter.cc. For further information on the processing of your personal data by Twitter and the corresponding objection options, please click here:

Twitter: [https://twitter.com/de/privacy](https://twitter.com/de/privacy)

##### IX. Hosting

The website is hosted on servers of a service provider commissioned by us.

Our service provider is:

OVH GmbH  
Christophstraße 19  
50670 Köln  
Deutschland

The servers automatically collect and store information in so-called server log files, which your browser automatically transmits when you visit the website. The stored information is:

* Browser type and version
* Used operating system
* Referrer URL
* Hostname of the accessing computer
* Time and date of the server request
* IP address of the user's device

This data will not be merged with other data sources. The data is collected on the basis of Art. 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the technically error-free presentation and optimization of his website - and server log files are therefore recorded.

The server of the website is geographically located in the European Union (EU) or the European Economic Area (EEA).

##### X. Geotargeting

We use the IP address and other information provided by the user (e.g. the postal code used for registration or ordering) to approach regional target groups (so-called "geotargeting").

The regional target group approach is used, for example, to automatically display regional offers or advertisements that often are more relevant to users. The legal basis for the use of the IP address and any other information provided by the user (e.g. postal code) is Art. 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR, based on our legitimate interest in ensuring a more precise target group approach and thus providing offers and advertising with greater relevance for our users.

Part of the IP address and the additional information provided by the user (e.g. postal code) are merely processed and not stored separately.

You can prevent geotargeting by, for example, using a VPN or proxy server that prevents accurate localisation. In addition, depending on the browser you are using, you can also deactivate a location localisation in the corresponding browser settings (as far as this is supported by the respective browser).

We use geotargeting on our website for the following purposes:

* Geoblocking

##### XI. Affiliate programs

We also use the following partner programs:

Monetag.com

Further information on the collection and storage of data by Monetag can be found here: https://monetag.com/privacy/

##### XII. Content delivery networks

1\. Description and scope of data processing

On our website we use functions of the content delivery network OVHcloud of OVH GmbH (Hereinafter referred to as OVHcloud). A Content Delivery Network (CDN) is a network of regionally distributed servers connected via the Internet to deliver content, especially large media files such as videos. OVHcloud offers web optimization and security services that we use to improve the load times of our website and to protect it from misuse. When you visit our website you will be connected to the servers of OVHcloud, e.g. to retrieve content. This allows personal data to be stored and evaluated in server log files, the user's activity (e.g. which pages have been visited) and device and browser information (e.g. IP address and operating system). Further information on the collection and storage of data by OVHcloud can be found here: https://www.ovhcloud.com/de/personal-data-protection/

2\. Purpose of data processing

The use of OVHcloud features serves to deliver and accelerate online applications and content.

3\. Legal basis for data processing

The data is collected on the basis of Art. 6 (1) (1) (f) GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the technically error-free presentation and optimization of his website -and the server log files are therefore recorded.

4\. Duration of storage

Your personal information will be retained for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or as required by law.

5\. Objection and removal

Information about objection and removal options regarding OVHcloud can be found at:  
https://www.ovhcloud.com/de/personal-data-protection/

© 2024 [Clip Converter](https://www.clipconverter.cc/) - Free Online Media Conversion and Download - [Terms of Use](https://www.clipconverter.cc/terms/) - [Privacy](https://www.clipconverter.cc/terms/#privacy) - [Imprint](https://www.clipconverter.cc/imprint/)
